<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mackenzie Bligh</title>
    <link>https://mack1070101.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mackenzie Bligh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 18:18:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mack1070101.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://mack1070101.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 21:43:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack1070101.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Employment Backend Software Engineer: Turo Nov 2018 - Present
Turo is the largest Peer-to-Peer car sharing platform that operates in the United States, Canada, the U.K. and Germany.
 Designed, and implemented the back end for Turo Go Digital: a software solution to remotely lock, unlock, and pull state from vehicles Worked with Java, Kotlin, and MySQL Participated in cross functional product teams; collaborate with stakeholders across domains within and external to the company Completed a significant upgrade of Turo&amp;rsquo;s vehicle delivery product to allow delivery to airports, hotels, and other points of interest Ran interviews for hiring new back end engineers  Backend Software Engineer: Copia Sept 2017 - Nov 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming</title>
      <link>https://mack1070101.github.io/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 18:31:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack1070101.github.io/programming/</guid>
      <description>Projects Fotingo-emacs   fotingo-emacs is an Emacs interface to the cli tool fotingo. Fotingo is a CLI to ease the interaction between Git, Github and Jira when working on tasks. fotingo-emacs aims to provide the same level of convenience provided by Magit and is designed to follow a similar workflow.
dotfiles Configuration for all the tools I use; .spacemacs may be of interest for Emacs enthusiasts.
DynamoInverter A library for turning DynamoDb QuerySpec and ScanSpec objects into SQL strings that can be processed by JDBC to standardize database interactions around AWS objects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal</title>
      <link>https://mack1070101.github.io/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 18:18:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mack1070101.github.io/interests/</guid>
      <description>Outdoor Hiking  For day hikes, look at satellite views first to determine if it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;road&amp;rdquo; hike For COVID-19 hikes you need to drive a couple hours away from the city to miss crowds Always plan a fallback hike Bring chairs/comfort items on day hikes  North America  Pinancles National Park. Good day trip Gold Bluffs beach campground  Almost a 7 hour drive No reservations after sept 28   Zion national park traverse Graeagle is apparently a cool spot to go Hiking(from Jack Trout)    Completed</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>